A Guide to the Harry Atwood Film Collection, 1949-1995.
Harry Atwood Film Collection
- RESTRICTED MATERIALS, II.; FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 2000-97/1 (07993190))
  - VIDEO VHS AND 3/4 INCH:: (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - A Portrait of Mexico, 1962 (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - The Aged Land, 1961 (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - Christmas Music of the Southwest, 1955 (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - The Great Unfenced, 1963 (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - Home movies, 1962-1992 [From 16mm film], FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
  - Video VHS and 3/4 inch: (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
    - De Grazia (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
    - The Last Wagon (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
    - Terra Sancta (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
    - On one VHS and one 3/4 inch videocassette: (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
      - University of Symphony Orchestra, 1957 (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
      - The Kress Collection, 1957 (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
      - A Portrait of Europe, 1960, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 95-273/2 (04913923))
  - VHS videocassette tape: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
    - Transferred from 8mm film: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - To Build A Fire, 1953 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - The Telephone Call, 1954 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
  - Audio cassette tapes: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
    - Finished tracks: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - To Build a Fire, 1953 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - The Telephone Call, 1954 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
  - 3/4 inch videocassette tape: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
    - Transferred from 8mm film: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - Outpost, 1949 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - The Carabi Incident, 1951 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - Through the Valley, 1946 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
      - Family Album, 1941 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
  - 8mm film originals: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
    - Outpost, 1949 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
    - The Carabi Incident, 1951 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
    - Through the Valley, 1946 (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
  - Two Original 1/4″ Phonotapes: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
    - Atwood's Master's Recital, 1954, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 96-308/2 (04991698))
  - 16mm film [originals]: (Box 94-124/1 (05228414))
    - Adagio, H-586, A and B rolls, ECO (Box 94-124/1 (05228414))
    - Genesis, I-226, A and B rolls, ECO (Box 94-124/1 (05228414))
    - High on the Wild, A/WIND I. R. (Box 94-124/1 (05228414))
    - Alaska, R1-36, B49598, July 29, 1986, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 94-124/1 (05228414))
    - High on the Wild, A and B rolls, ECN, J-105 (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - Back of Beyond, A and B rolls, Rev. 972' (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - High on the Wild, B/WIND, 35/32, So213, D33532 (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - High on the Wild, work print, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 94-124/2 (05228844))
    - Cajititlan, September 18, 1978 (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Fantasmas, July 25, 1978 (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Fire on the Sea (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Fire on the Sea, May 13, 1980 (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Fire on the Sea, May 9, 1980 (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Christmas Music of the Southwest (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Portrait of Europe (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Fever, July 28, 1977, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/1 (6196255))
    - Fever, July 28, 1977 (Box 97-037/2 (6196404))
    - The Clowns Never Laugh, C-roll, April 11, 1967 (Box 97-037/2 (6196404))
    - The Clowns Never Laugh, A and B roll, April 11, 1967 (Box 97-037/2 (6196404))
    - A Portrait of Europe, Roll I-C titles (Box 97-037/2 (6196404))
    - The Clowns Never Laugh, magnetic track, April 11, 1967 (Box 97-037/2 (6196404))
    - Yankee Painter, C-roll (Box 97-037/2 (6196404))
    - Fire on the Sea, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/2 (6196404))
    - Paths in the Wilderness, August 4, 1976 (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - Paths in the Wilderness, August 4, 1976 (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - Paths in the Wilderness, B, August 4, 1976 wind (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - Paths in the Wilderness, August 4, 1976 (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - Fantasmas, September 5, 1978 (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - A Masterpiece of Spanish Painting, original, C-roll (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - A Masterpiece of Spanish Painting, master, C-roll (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - Aged Land, original, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/3 (6196380))
    - Bridge to the East, negative #2 (Box 97-037/4 (6196379))
    - Paths in the Wilderness (Box 97-037/4 (6196379))
    - Bridge to the East (Box 97-037/4 (6196379))
    - Journey Thru Eden, Jack West associates (Box 97-037/4 (6196379))
    - Fantasmas, "B" Wind, July 25, 1978 (Box 97-037/4 (6196379))
    - Cajititlan, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/4 (6196379))
    - Cajititlan (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Cajititlan, December 8, 1977 (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Journey Thru Eden, Jack West associates (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Fever (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Fantasmas (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Portrait of Mexico (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Christmas Music of the Southwest, magnetic track (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Christmas Music of the Southwest, "B" wind, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/5 (6196390))
    - Fever, "B" wind (Box 97-037/6 (6196266))
    - Journey Thru Eden, Jack West associates (Box 97-037/6 (6196266))
    - A Masterpiece of Spanish Painting, original (Box 97-037/6 (6196266))
    - Portrait of Europe, original (Box 97-037/6 (6196266))
    - Portrait of Europe, "B" wind negative (Box 97-037/6 (6196266))
    - Portrait of Mexico, "B" wind negative, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/7 (6196583))
    - Portrait of Mexico (Box 97-037/7 (6196583))
    - Tiger by the Tail (Box 97-037/7 (6196583))
    - Terra Sancta, May 7, 1968 (Box 97-037/7 (6196583))
    - Charles Burchfield, June 21, 1966 (Box 97-037/7 (6196583))
    - Bellota, May 1, 1969 (Box 97-037/7 (6196583))
    - Terra Sancta, May 9, 1968, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/7 (6196583))
    - Tiger by the Tail, December 21, 1971 (Box 97-037/8 (6196211))
    - Tiger by the Tail, recut (Box 97-037/8 (6196211))
    - John Marin, March 12, 1968 (Box 97-037/8 (6196211))
    - John Marin, June 7, 1968 (Box 97-037/8 (6196211))
    - John Marin, March 14, 1968 (Box 97-037/8 (6196211))
    - John Marin, August 6, 1968, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/8 (6196211))
    - The Clowns Never Laugh, April 19, 1967 (Box 97-037/9 (6195059))
    - Charles Burchfield, Fifty Years of His Art, June 21, 1966 (Box 97-037/9 (6195059))
    - Charles Burchfield, Fifty Years of His Art, June 23, 1966 (Box 97-037/9 (6195059))
    - Tiger by the Tail, December 21, 1971 (Box 97-037/9 (6195059))
    - Tiger by the Tail (Box 97-037/9 (6195059))
    - Bellota, May 23, 1969, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/9 (6195059))
    - A Masterpiece of Spanish Painting (Box 97-037/10 (6196222))
    - Aged Land, magnetic track (Box 97-037/10 (6196222))
    - Aged Land, original (Box 97-037/10 (6196222))
    - John Marin, March 12, 1968 (Box 97-037/10 (6196222))
    - The Last Wagon, February 2, 1971 (Box 97-037/10 (6196222))
    - The Last Wagon, February 17, 1971 (Box 97-037/10 (6196222))
    - A Masterpiece of Spanish Painting, work print, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/10 (6196222))
    - Bridge to the East, Jack West associates (Box 97-037/11 (6195048))
    - Bridge to the East, Jack West associates (Box 97-037/11 (6195048))
    - The Great Unfenced, B-roll original (Box 97-037/11 (6195048))
    - The Great Unfenced, inter-negative (Box 97-037/11 (6195048))
    - The Great Unfenced, B wind, negative (Box 97-037/11 (6195048))
    - Bellota, May 16, 1969 (Box 97-037/11 (6195048))
    - Aged Land, A wind negative, FOR PRESERVATION ONLY, not for Public Use: (Box 97-037/11 (6195048))
    - Bridge to the East, Jack West associates, B wind, magnetic track (Box 97-037/12 (6196244))
    - The Great Unfenced, A and C originals (Box 97-037/12 (6196244))
    - Terra Sancta, final magnetic track (Box 97-037/12 (6196244))
    - A Portrait of Mexico, final magnetic track, May 24, 1976 (Box 97-037/12 (6196244))
    - Christmas Music of the Southwest, work print, ORIGINAL MATERIALS RESTRICTED. NEED DONOR PERMISSION: (Box 97-037/12 (6196244))
    - American Realists, GFL-075412, 1965 (Box 94-200/1 (05228822))
      - Part 1: (Box 94-200/1 (05228822))
        - A-C rolls (Box 94-200/1 (05228822))
        - Mag. track (Box 94-200/1 (05228822))
        - B-Wind, neg. track (Box 94-200/1 (05228822))
      - Part 2: (Box 94-200/1 (05228822))
        - A-B rolls, ORIGINAL MATERIALS RESTRICTED. NEED DONOR PERMISSION: (Box 94-200/1 (05228822))
        - C rolls (Box 94-200/2 (05228833))
        - B-Wind, neg. track (Box 94-200/2 (05228833))
    - Summer Odyssey, DEL-148017, 1972 (Box 94-200/2 (05228833))
      - 16 mm, A and B rolls (Box 94-200/2 (05228833))
      - Neg. track (Box 94-200/2 (05228833))
      - Mag. track (Box 94-200/2 (05228833))